CHANDANA SUGGALA

408-390-5110 – csuggala@gmail.com http://www.linkedin.com/in/chandanasuggala

PROJECT MANAGEMENT LEADER

Results-driven project leader with a strong record of managing complex projects and leading strategic initiatives that drive business growth. Experienced in portfolio governance, M&A integrations, and program management, aiming to deliver exceptional outcomes for organizations.

PROJECT MANAGEMENT EXPERTISE

- Project Roadmap Execution
- Project Rescues/Turnarounds
- Portfolio Management
- Global/Multi-Site Projects
- Change Management
- Mergers & Acquisitions
 System Integration Projects
- Program Management
- Enterprise Business Applications
- Global Expansions

EXPERIENCE

PagerDuty, San Francisco, CA

Feb 2019 - Aug 2023

IT PMO

- Led international expansion initiative in Japan, including entity setup, hiring, and process development, localization of systems, resulting in revenue generation.
- Managed successful integrations of Rundeck, Catalytic, and VariaCode acquisitions into PagerDuty, standardizing integration processes. Created an M&A Playbook.
- Managed high-priority strategic initiatives for GTM expansion in Chile and Portugal, Sales Enablement, and system implementations for Opportunity to Cash (O2C), Salesforce CPQ, Workday, Zuora, Coupa, and NetSuite..
- Oversaw crisis operations during the pandemic that involved various initiatives to support employees and adapting GTM strategy and execution to meet customer needs.
- Spearheaded a company-wide strategic initiative with top-level executives resulting in the achievement of the company's revenue and pipeline objectives for the fiscal year..
- Established and oversaw a 'change management' committee of ~30 key cross-functional stakeholders to enhance transparency and foster alignment among different functional teams.
- Built and led a PMO team, establishing standardized processes for portfolio governance, project management, and change management.

Marketo (Adobe), San Mateo, CA

Aug 2014 - Jan 2019

Senior Manager, IT

Oct 2016 - Jan 2019

- Successfully managed IT portfolio projects, including M&A integrations, Salesforce CPQ, PureCloud, FinancialForce, Conga Novatus CLM, BI, RingCentral, Concur, LMS, and ASC 606/GDPR compliance.
- Led the Salesforce Reboot project, enhancing user experience and security.
- Successfully led the product launch of Account Based Marketing (ABM) that involved cross functional teams of 100+ members from across the globe representing Product, Engineering,

Chandana Suggala Page 1

PS, Partners, Solution Consulting, Sales, Finance, Marketing, IT, and Legal. functions, within "mission impossible" timelines.

Managed a 7-person PMO team and established standardized processes and governance.

Senior IT Project Manager

Aug 2014 – Sep 2016

- Led a cross-functional team of 40+ people in transitioning to a streamlined Salesforce CPQ.
- Successfully delivered multiple cross-functional projects, exceeding user expectations.
- Streamlined project management processes for broader use.

Senior Project Manager/Business Analyst, Infoblox

May 2011-June 2014

- Successfully led strategic projects Salesforce PRM, RightNow Customer Service Portal, Infoblox.com, Point of Sale Portal, SOX Compliance, Data Center move, and Oracle ERP.
- Established the foundation for an IT PMO by creating project management processes and templates.

Lead IT Business Analyst (Finance), Neopost USA

July 2001 – May 2011

• Led projects for Oracle Application software solutions/enhancements, including system upgrades and compliance projects.

Other Projects

• Worked internationally in the UK, Singapore, and India on Oracle ERP implementations.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified ScrumMaster, 2018
- Program Management Certification, UC Berkeley - 2016
- ICAgile Certification 2016
- PMP Certified Professional, 2013
- Project Management Certification, UC Berkeley, 2007
- Post Graduate Diploma in Computer Sciences, BDPS, India
- Bachelor's Degree, India

Citizenship Info: US Citizen

Chandana Suggala Page 2